<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on WittyJudge</title>
    <link>https://wittyjudge.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on WittyJudge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wittyjudge.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TCP Header</title>
      <link>https://wittyjudge.github.io/posts/tcp-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wittyjudge.github.io/posts/tcp-header/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In TCP, each segment consist of data that are sent to the receiver&amp;rsquo;s server.
Alongside the data, the TCP segment contains header which holds information about the connection and the current data being sent.
The TCP header size can range from 20 bytes (160 bits) to 60 bytes (480 bits), with 20 bytes designated for 10 mandatory fields and 40 bytes for optional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The table of TCP header is shown bellow:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux Printer Install with CUPS</title>
      <link>https://wittyjudge.github.io/posts/arch-linux-printer-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wittyjudge.github.io/posts/arch-linux-printer-install/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been using Arch Linux for about 3 years now and only recently I needed to print and scan documents with my office printer (Canon MF260).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preconfigured Linux distros like Ubuntu, Mint, Manjaro, etc.. already provided you with some functionality to use your printer/scanner.
All you need to do is just log in to your favorite DE, search for &amp;ldquo;printer&amp;rdquo; in the application launcher, click on the &amp;ldquo;Add a printer&amp;rdquo; button and it will magically discover your Wi-Fi wireless or plugged-in printer, install all drivers for that specific printer and&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s ready for use.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to set up WireGuard on your own Ubuntu 20.04 server</title>
      <link>https://wittyjudge.github.io/posts/setup-wireguard-vpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wittyjudge.github.io/posts/setup-wireguard-vpn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wireguard.com/&#34;&gt;WireGuard&lt;/a&gt; is a lightweight communication protocol that implements encrypted virtual privacy network (VPN).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In my humble opinion, if you are simple user, you should use VPN, because:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It gives you more freedom to access the internet safely from your smartphone or laptop when connected to a doubt network, like any public WiFi.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have an access to websites blocked in your country for some reasons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;!-- **Here are just a few reasons why WireGuard is so awesome:** --&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wireguard-is-so-awesome-but-why&#34;&gt;WireGuard is so awesome. But why?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;minimal-code-base&#34;&gt;Minimal code base&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s implemented in less then 4,000 lines of code.
It&amp;rsquo;s much &lt;strong&gt;easier to audit and reviewing the code&lt;/strong&gt; for security vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
